ourloot2boot.com 2013-11-27

# OurLoot2Boot Network

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.ourloot2boot.com. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. OurLoot2Boot respects your privacy. Our purpose in collecting information from you, is to help us provide you with better service.

**Information Collection and Use**

OurLoot2Boot is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way. OurLoot2Boot collects information from our users at several different points on our web site.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For example, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to input a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. We also use cookies to allow user customization on various areas of our site. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Email**

We use the return name and email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses and names are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties other than our business partner "MRMerchandise". They too agree to never share or sell your email address.

**Site and Service Updates**

We also send the user site and service announcement updates.

**Outbound Links to Other Web Sites**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

If it is determined that you are scamming people and/or frauding offers, certain information about you, and/or your history, will be shared with other site owners/operators in our on-going community efforts to combat scamming/fraud.
